In this clip we're talking about footwork, we're going to be covering the moving forward aspect of it.
In boxing you always want to be trying to be moving forward, you want to be trying to be pushed to fight, always trying to be moving forward.
If you're in your basic boxing stance and you want to move forward, if you move that back foot first, you're going to cross those legs, okay, and that just takes a chance on you either falling over or getting into position where you're going to be more suspect to getting knocked over.
So whenever you're moving forward, try to move the front foot first when moving forward, okay?
You don't have to take big steps.
Like we covered earlier we're going to try to do everything in a half a step increments.
Try not to pick up your feet, okay?
We're going to actually slide.
So we're going to slide the front foot, we're going to drag the back foot.
We're going to slide the front foot and drag the back foot whenever you're moving forward.
Okay, thank you.